<OTHEREXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2019 June</TIME>
		<COURSE>Spring: The Big Picture</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>Pluralsight by Dustin Schultz</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Spring Boot, auto-configurations, Spring Core, Web MVC, AOP, Data access, testing, data project, cloud project, security project</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2019 June</TIME>
		<COURSE>Angular: Getting Started</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>Pluralsight by Deborah Kurata</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Components, interpolation, directives, data binding, pipes, dependency injection, HTTP, routing, and Angular CLI</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2019 June</TIME>
		<COURSE>Hacking the User Experience: UX for Developers</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>Pluralsight by Keith Harvey</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Cognitive Biases, User-Centered design, UX Myths and Pitfalls, effects of whitespace, shapes, alignment and color, power of recognition, cognitive friction</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2019 May</TIME>
		<COURSE>PHP basics</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>CodeCourse</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>MAMP, variables, array, concatination, if-statements, switch-statements, basic arithmetics, loops, functions, scope, POST- and GET superglobals</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2019 May</TIME>
		<COURSE>Outsystems</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>Outsystems</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Low Code platform. Made a simple moviedatabase that is linked to a example database. Users could sort movies and actors, movie details were displayed per movie, admin could add and remove movies and actors, and users could rate the movie which is immediatly updated and calculated with the average score with AJAX.</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2019 January</TIME>
		<COURSE>Java Bootcamp</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>ITPH</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Java SE8 OCA topics, Spring, Hibernate and JPA, HTTP, REST, SQL, Angular, UML, Git and Github, typescript, Bootstrap, Postman, Visual Studio Code</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2018 November</TIME>
		<COURSE>Java Programming Masterclass for Software Developers</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>Udemy, by Tim Buchalka</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Variables, operators, datatypes, control flow statements, composition, encapsulation, polymorphism, inheritance, constructors, classes, auto- and unboxing, arrays, lists, abstract class and interface, generics, basic I/O, Lambda and streams, exceptions, debugging and unit testing.</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2018</TIME>
		<COURSE>Introduction to Javascript</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>CodeCademy</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Conditionals, functions, scope, arrays, loops, iterators, objects, classes</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2018</TIME>
		<COURSE>Learn CSS</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>CodeCademy</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Selectors, box-model, position and display, colors, typography, grid</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2017</TIME>
		<COURSE>Introduction to HTML</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>CodeCademy</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Elements and structure, tables, forms, css</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2017</TIME>
		<COURSE>Video tutorials on Java</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>Youtube, by Buck Roberts (TheNewBoston)</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>JDK, Eclipse, variables, user input, calculator, operators, classes, methods and parameters, constructors, loops, arrays, access modifiers, getters and setters, toString, enum, static, final, GUI with JFrame, event handler, overriding, polymorphism, reading and writing files.</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2016</TIME>
		<COURSE>Homestudy Java Programming </COURSE>
		<COMPANY>LOI</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Variables, objects, operators, if-statements, loops, arrays, encapsulation, methods, inheritance and exceptions</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2015</TIME>
		<COURSE>Video tutorials about C++</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>Youtube, by LearningLad</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Constants, variables, data types, keywords, cout and cin, comments, operators, if-statements, loops, multi-dimensional arrays, parameters and functions, scope, break- and continue statements, return statements</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
	<EXPERIENCE>
		<TIME>2008</TIME>
		<COURSE>First experimenting with HTML</COURSE>
		<COMPANY>Various inspirations</COMPANY>
		<OTHER>Looked at elements from anime fanwebpages what effects I liked, search it up in their source code, and tried it out on my webpage</OTHER>
	</EXPERIENCE>
</OTHEREXPERIENCE>